yellowpages-uae.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy policies of online business directory Yellow Pages UAE. yellowpages-uae.com

### Privacy & Policy

This site is owned and operated by Lunad Digital Portal. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Lunad, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Internet Privacy Policy at any time. This Internet Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site. We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the web site.

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our web site, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual ("personal information"). This Internet Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with.

##### Information Lunad gathers and tracks:

Lunad gathers two types of information about users.

 **Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions**. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to get listed on our website(s) and to email a friend.

 **Information Lunad gathers through aggregated tracking information** derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because Lunad derives its revenue mainly from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. Under no circumstances does Lunad divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

##### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

##### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##### Links to other websites

Our website contains links to other websites based on user interaction.. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

##### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
